http://www.knapeandvogt.com/content/privacy-policy

Menu
AboutCorporate ProfileMissionKV Fact SheetAnnouncementsLeadershipCareer OpportunitiesTrade AssociationsQuality PolicyContact UsProductsNew ProductsFeatured ProductsBarn Door HardwareCloset HardwareDrawer SlidesErgonomic SolutionsGarage OrganizationKitchen & BathShelvingSliding Door HardwareSpecialty HardwareIndustry SolutionsAppliancesAutomotiveElectronic EquipmentHealthcareOffice FurnitureTool StorageWorkplace ErgonomicsHome SolutionsCloset HardwareDrawer SlidesGarage OrganizationKitchen & BathShelvingSliding Door HardwareKV Connect BlogOur BrandsKV®KV GSlide® KV Tru-Trac® KV DuriSlide® HyLoft®Real Solutions for Real LifeJohn Sterling®Shelf-Made® Closet Culture™StoreBarn Door HardwareCloset HardwareDrawer SlidesGarage OrganizationKitchen & BathShelvingSliding Door HardwareSpecialty Hardware
Resource Library
Customer Service
Shopping Cart
Contact Us
Login
Mobile Main Menu
About Corporate Profile
Mission
Menu
AboutCorporate ProfileMissionKV Fact SheetAnnouncementsLeadershipCareer OpportunitiesTrade AssociationsQuality PolicyContact UsProductsNew ProductsFeatured ProductsBarn Door HardwareCloset HardwareDrawer SlidesErgonomic SolutionsGarage OrganizationKitchen & BathShelvingSliding Door HardwareSpecialty HardwareIndustry SolutionsAppliancesAutomotiveElectronic EquipmentHealthcareOffice FurnitureTool StorageWorkplace ErgonomicsHome SolutionsCloset HardwareDrawer SlidesGarage OrganizationKitchen & BathShelvingSliding Door HardwareKV Connect BlogOur BrandsKV®KV GSlide® KV Tru-Trac® KV DuriSlide® HyLoft®Real Solutions for Real LifeJohn Sterling®Shelf-Made® Closet Culture™StoreBarn Door HardwareCloset HardwareDrawer SlidesGarage OrganizationKitchen & BathShelvingSliding Door HardwareSpecialty Hardware
Privacy Policy
Knape & Vogt Manufacturing Company ("KV") is the sole owner of kv.com and knapeandvogt.com (the "Site") and the information collected on the Site. This Privacy Policy sets forth the guidelines KV uses for protecting the information you ("User" or "you") provide to KV during visits to the Site. By using this Site, you acknowledge that you have reviewed, and accept and agree to, the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If you do not accept and agree to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, do not use the Site.
1. INFORMATION COLLECTED. When you visit kv.com, you may provide us with different types of information: Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our web Site and personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis.
Normal Web Site Usage: You can visit the Site to access information regarding KV and KV's products without submitting any personal information. KV reserves the right to collect and store during normal Site usage certain nonpersonally identifiable information, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the type of web browser and operating system you use, the web site that referred you to the Site, the pages you request and the date and time of those requests. KV uses this type of passively collected information for several purposes, such as to administer the Site, to measure Site activity, and for marketing and research purposes. KV receives and stores certain types of information whenever you visit our Site through the use of "cookies." A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. The Site may use cookies so that KV can better serve you when you return to the Site. In most instances, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you a chance to decide whether to accept it.
Personal Information You Choose to Provide: At various points on this Site, you may choose to actively provide certain kinds of information, including personally identifiable information. Personal information is gathered only when Users make voluntary online submissions of such information or voluntarily establish an account. For example, we request information from you when you set up an online customer, dealer or supplier account, and when you purchase products online. The types of information we collect depends on the nature of the account, and such personal information may include: name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card number, social security number, job title, and employer. We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give in any other way.
Online Account Usage: KV provides certain Users with the opportunity to sign up for an online account which permits an online User to access a password-protected portion of the Site. The online account portions of the Site are restricted to authorized Users. In order to become an authorized User, you may be required to complete a registration form that asks for a variety of information that will allow KV to identify you. Such personally identifiable information may include your: name, email address, address, telephone phone number credit card number, social security number, job title, and employer. By submitting information on this Site, you specifically consent to the collection, aggregation, use and dissemination of such information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for the accuracy of the personal information and providing KV with any necessary corrections, updates and changes.
Email: This Site provides you with the opportunity to submit questions or comments or request additional information from KV. KV may use the information you provide in your email to respond to your questions or comments, and KV specifically reserves the right to retain whatever information you submit, including your name, email address and any questions or comments submitted.
2. WHO SHOULD USE THIS SITE. This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and KV will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from such individuals. This Site is controlled, operated and administered by KV from its offices in the United States of America. KV explicitly disclaims any expressed or implied representation that this Site is appropriate or available for viewing in any other country, territory or jurisdiction outside of the United States of America. For further limitations, see KV's Terms of Use.
3. OTHER USES OF INFORMATION. KV will not trade, rent or sell your personal information. As indicated above, KV uses the information collected from you on the Site for a variety of purposes. KV uses the personal information collected for purposes of administering KV’s business activities, providing customer service, and making products and services available to KV’s customers. Occasionally, KV may also use the information KV collects to notify you about important changes to the Site, new services and special information KV thinks you might find valuable. Users who do not wish to receive those mailings (whether e-mail or paper mail) or who believe they are receiving those mailings by mistake can contact KV and request removal from the mailing list by e-mail or toll-free at 1-800-253-1561 between 8 a.m. and 5p.m. EST Monday - Friday.
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy or elsewhere on this Site, KV reserves the right to share any information you submit on this Site in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this Site and/or KV; to respond to law enforcement requests; to enforce or apply the Terms of Use or other agreements; to protect the rights, property or safety of kv.com and our users, or where required by applicable law, regulation, subpoena, or court order. By submitting personally identifiable information on this Site, you consent to such disclosures in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.
4. SHARING INFORMATION WITH OUTSIDE PARTIES. From time to time we may share the information we collect with agents, contractors or affiliates of KV for the purpose of providing services to KV. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill Users for products. When the User signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
5. SECURITY. Although KV takes reasonable steps to protect any personally identifiable information provided on this Site from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration, no system is 100% secure or error-free. Therefore, KV does not guarantee the security or accuracy of the information collected on this Site, and you acknowledge that you are assuming the risk in transmitting such information to us. KV works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you provide to us. To be sure your connection is secure, look at the lower portion of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser), the SSL is active. Access to the Password-Protected Account portions of the Site are password protected to prevent unauthorized access, use or improper disclosure of information. It is your responsibility to safeguard any usernames and passwords you use to access portions of this Site and to notify KV if you believe such usernames or passwords are being misused. You acknowledge that you are solely responsible for any unauthorized use of this Site conducted with your username and/or password.
6. SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY/LINKS. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site. Although KV may provide hyperlinks on this Site to other web sites, those web sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If User links to these sites, User will leave this Site and User does so at User's own risk. You should read the privacy policy of every web site you visit, including those web sites to which this Site provides links. KV makes no warranty or representation regarding any linked web sites or the information appearing on such linked sites. The links do not imply that KV sponsors, endorses, is affiliated or associated with, or is legally authorized to use any trademark, trade name, logo or copyright symbol displayed in the linked sites.
7. QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS. If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or this Site, please contact KV in one of the following ways:
By Email: customer.service@kv.com
By Mail: Attn: Legal Services
Knape & Vogt Manufacturing Company
2700 Oak Industrial Drive
Grand Rapids, Michigan 49505
8. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. KV reserves the right to revise or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time and post such revisions or modifications on the Site. Continued use of the Site after any such revision or modification constitutes User's acceptance of the Privacy Policy as so revised or modified. If this Privacy Policy is revised, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on the Site with the date of the most recent version.
9. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS. By using this Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
10. OPT OUT. Our users are given the opportunity to "Opt Out" of having their personal information disclosed, used or distributed to third-parties and the opportunity to "Opt Out" of having us use the personal information for a purpose which is incompatible with the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the User. To "Opt Out" either request by e-mail or contact us toll-free at 1.800.253.1561 between 8 a.m. and 5 p.m. EST Monday – Friday.
Connect
Find a Distributor
HyLoft Installer Locator
Contact Us
Catalogs
Hardware Catalog
Home Storage & Organization Catalog
Barn Door Hardware Catalog
